Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is a time known as
the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide.
Raise the sails and take the helm!
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals?
Is only legendary.
Till someone proves it real!
Through it all.
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there.
To stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
Oh right they want to fight too huh?
Now this will be fun!
Okay pops you promised me remember.
If I run those pirates off
then my debt to you is clear!
No more chores that's the deal.
There's no telling how much more of my
restaurants you could screw
up if you stick around.
Yeah so kid you said you were going to
be king of the pirates were you serious?
If we can capture that ship, the Grand
Line will be ours for the taking.
No more pretending to be Marines or
raising the white flag of surrender.
None of our enemies will suspect that
we're a threat with a ship like that.
In that boat, it'll
always be a sneak attack.
He's right.
That boat would come in handy.
No one would think that pirates were
on such a ridiculous-looking ship.
Right, but Don,
even if we enter the Grand
Line again using that vessel,
what if we come across someone
like Hawkeye Mihawk again?
Then what will we do?
I really appreciate the input,
sailor. Anything else? No! No!
Do you think an ordinary man could
cut up a sailing ship like that?
That man probably has the
power of the Devil Fruit.
Although those with Devil Fruit
powers are rare and legendary to us,
I assure you they're
commonplace on the Grand Line.
Mihawk must have used some sort of strange
power when he sliced our ship to ribbons.
When we're on the Grand Line,
those powers won't be special.
Even the Straw Hat Freak
will be considered normal.
That old geezer Redfoot Zeff
sailed those seas for a year.
It stands to reason that he had strategies
for dealing with those monsters.
The techniques for
surviving that parade of
weirdos must be written
in the old man's logbook.
Along with clues to the One Piece.
I see, you're a genius.
All we have to do is get
that logbook in the ship.
Then we'll be able to find our
way to the One Piece again.
You hear that, boys?
Now let's get to it!
The restaurant will be ours!
You pirate scum are gonna
have to get through us first!
Go to the control room and
open up the fins. What? No!
That's a bad idea!
If we do that, we'll be
giving the enemy a foothold!
And that's just fine.
We gotta do whatever it takes to
keep those guys out of this place.
If they destroy the inside, then
the old man will complain forever.
Did you just say something, you brat?
Yeah, I said you're whiny now go yes, sir!
Did you see that go kid?
What the heck's up with that guy?
Yeah, he's crazy!
It's hard to believe!
The Grand Line is crawling
with guys like these.
Sanji, pay special attention
to how this one fights!
So let me get this straight: you're
attacking the restaurant that gave you food.
I got no choice but To
beat some manners into you!
So you want to fight on the water
where there's no place to stand?
Huh a bold move for someone like you the
Devil Fruit has taken your ability to swim.
Hasn't it your boy? Yeah, but now
Now we have somewhere to fight him.
Whoa!
That's so cool!
My cooks and I will never
give up defending this place.
Prepare to die. I see.
Good plan, bringing up all
that extra decking, genius.
Now we don't have to
take the fight inside.
I'd hate to damage my future ship.
And make no mistake, it will be mine!
We will never let you have the restaurant!
That's right!
We mean business!
We're battle cooks now!
Sanseo Mackerel Head One,
the Baratie's secret weapon!
So, if you want to live, I
suggest running away now!
What is that thing?
That thing is so cool!
Paddle faster!
You paddle faster!
Fire!
Those guys are gonna sink
me too! Yeah! Get him!
Yeah!
Get him, guys! Get him!
Blow them away!
You can do it!
Nice!
Keep your eyes on the prize, Patty!
This one counts!
Right!
Krieg, say your prayers!
Little did you know that
the Sea Restaurant Baratier
had such a powerful weapon
just waiting to be unleashed!
What happened?
Did we bump into something?
We're not moving!
I am Don Creed!
The man who will rule the oceans!
Oh no you're not! I am!
I don't have time for these stupid games!
Get out of here!
No way!
He's so strong!
It's coming straight for us!
The restaurant! Oh, no!
Salute!
No way!
He's got legs of steel.
He kicked back that crazy
boat just like it was nothing.
Very impressive.
Nice kick.
What's the deal?
Are you trying to crush your friends?
Yeah, yeah.
Don't yeah, yeah us, you crazy fool.
Stop acting so cool!
You wouldn't be so smug if we'd
been killed, you bucket of backwash!
All right, ladies.
You think you could wrap
this up another time?
We have business to attend to.
Got them!
You guys still don't get it.
Even well-armed, you're still just cooks,
and we're expert fighters that
are way out of your league.
So why don't you be good little cooks
and run along to a safer restaurant,
maybe one on land, huh?
Come on, guys.
Why are you letting them
beat you up so easily, huh?
And you still call
yourselves fighting cucks.
Well, these pirates are really good.
They're totally different from
the ones we fought before.
It's insulting to lump us in
with that average riffraff.
We are the Great Creek Pirates, and we're
the absolute rulers of the East Blue.
Let it be known to all that
this garish boat already
belongs to the great and
powerful Creek Pirates.
You know what?
I've been a cook all my life.
I've worked at a lot of
restaurants and gotten
fired from them all for
scuffling and living hard.
And after years of wondering,
we finally found a home here.
Anybody here?
This is the restaurant that's owned
by a guy named Redfoot Zef, right?
Hey, we found this damn
Cook's Wanted sign.
Is it true?
Yeah, it's true.
But you need to understand that
this is no ordinary restaurant.
It really doesn't matter who
they are or where they come from.
If someone comes in hungry, we will
feed them until they're stuffed.
Do I make myself clear?
Can you handle that? Sir!
I wouldn't serve anyone's slap like this!
Hey, what'd you go and hit me for, huh?
Sure victory, sure defeat.
We like fighting and cooking, so this
place is perfect for us. That's right.
There's no other place like this.
You hear that?
Now that's true fighting spirit.
Committing ourselves to cooking fine cuisine
day in and day out is a fierce battle.
Compared to that, these
pirates are nothing.
He's right, yeah. Let's fight.
Protect Zep!
Protect the respawn!
Huh?
The hell was that?
Just what do you guys think you're doing?
Who's that?
So let's do this!
But before we begin, it's only fair.
I give you a warning.
I am Pearl the Invincible Shield!
Hey, it's Pearl Perona Carney!
Are you boys?
Okay, I'd say that pair is far from okay!
Those two just experienced
my Pearl Surprise!
One of my signature punches!
You bumbling, pathetic
idiot!
Hey, look at that!
Nice knife!
I think I'll take it! What?
Here!
Come on! Let it go!
I said, give it to me!
That
guy
knows how to
kick some serious butt!
A kitchen knife is a
cook's soul! How dare?
Why are you filthy pirates trying to
desecrate one with your grubby little hands?
Sanji.
Just stay down and hang on to this.
I'm gonna teach these bozos a lesson.
You must be out of your mind if you think
we're gonna be beaten by a mere cook!
I'll show you mere cook after I
fillet every one of you bastards.
Ha!
How very impudent of you to defeat
them all using only your kicks,
am I to be impressed by that?
I'm a cook, remember?
I couldn't do my job very well
if I ruined my hands in battle,
so I'll be taking you down with my feet.
Is that so?
I think not.
I'm invincible, you see.
I've won all 61 of my battles
completely and totally unscathed.
It's quite remarkable, really.
No one has ever shed a single drop
of my blood in battle. No one.
Now do you realize my power?
I may be a gentleman, but I'm not gentle.
Got it?
Was that supposed to be a joke?
Because it wasn't even a little bit funny.
Dropping your gun is a good
way to end up dead, you brat!
Even battleship cannons don't work on me.
I come out of any attack unharmed.
Boy, that could have been really bad.
Good thing I didn't fall into the ocean.
Oh, this isn't good. Blood! No!
Hey, Pearl, don't worry.
It's only a nosebleed, Pearl.
We know it's not a battle
wound, so just keep calm, okay?
What's this?
These people are just
mean. They're dangerous.
So, uh, want to tell me why
everyone's freaking out?
They're worried about a nosebleed?
Calm down!
It's just a nosebleed!
Don't lose your cool!
Relax!
Jeez, what is that guy doing?
Danger! Danger! Danger!
Who knew it started?
When he gets upset, he catches fire!
Uh, wait, what?
Fire pearls!
Special treats!
Perish in my flames!
With my shields and this
inferno, I am invincible!
That moron!
We need that ship and
he's gonna destroy it.
We're either gonna burn or drown.
He's destroying our only ship.
This isn't good.
The rest one's gonna catch fire.
Not on my watch!
Burn you!
Let you torch our dreams?
That guy's either brave or dumb.
That cook is gonna burn.
But these flames scare everyone away.
Well, if I was scared of fire,
I wouldn't be much of a cook.
I hate him.
I hate that refined gentleman.
Whoa, he got him good!
Yeah, he just broke through
Pearl's invincible wall!
You stupid cook!
You're totally insane!
I'll kill you!
Fire!
Need more fire!
Fire, Pearls!
No!
The whole boat's gonna burn!
If the blaze gets to the
kitchen, the ship will explode!
Run, Zaf! Get out of there! Run!
What? No way!
He put out my fire pearls!
Fire pearls, eh?
That's kid stuff.
Wow, the gust from his kick
put out all of those flames!
Impossible!
I don't believe it!
Redfoot Zef is still
just as strong as ever!
Way to go, Pops!
I'm impressed!
So, then it's finally
come down to this, huh?
I've got no choice.
Smash the fins or the boat burns!
Sanji, watch out!
He can't escape!
He's surrounded by fire!
Ouchie! The char boy!
Gum-Gum! Let's go!
He tossed that thing right back! Fire hot!
Carol is down!
And he's not gonna get out this time!
No!
Pearl!
So weird.
Yeah, that guy sure is goofy.
You want something done right?
You got no choice but to do it yourself.
The battle ends right here.
As a kid, I never stopped
searching for a great treasure.
I had a map in my mind
that I knew would leave me.
I had to find my way to that place
before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my
grasp and I wouldn't let go.
My only dream.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true!
But if the world ever
changes I call out your name.
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?